<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><div class="panel panel-default"><div class="table-responsive"><div class="card sb-card"><div class="card-block"><h3>Reviews created for <Strong>v_jaybhays</Strong> for sprint <Strong>Gortahork 4</Strong></h3><p>This gives a way to access review timelines, see revisions, see files, see comments, apply/reference key word indicators.</p></div></div><div class="panel-body"><table class="table"><thead><tr><th>
									#
								</th><th>
									Create Date
								</th><th>
									Summary
								</th><th>
									Revisions
								</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>1</td><td>10/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5289 : Update LeavePlanAvailability Entity to add new attributes minimumTime, minimumTimeIncrement and minimumTimeIncrementBasis </td><td/></tr><tr><td>2</td><td>10/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5277: DB changes to add new Subset to TimeUnits Enum Domain</td><td/></tr><tr><td>3</td><td>10/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5383: Add new Enum Domain \'MinimumTime\' along with the Domain Instances for A06-F02</td><td/></tr><tr><td>4</td><td>11/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5286: Correct the Eligibility-Criteria-Type for MinEE and Minimum No Of Employees rules.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>5</td><td>11/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5421 : Add Validation Rules and Validators for Minimum Time and minimum  Time Increment Fields on Leave Plan Availability Tab</td><td/></tr><tr><td>6</td><td>11/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5358 : UI Changes</td><td/></tr><tr><td>7</td><td>12/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5488: Update the enums/EvidenceResultType.java</td><td/></tr><tr><td>8</td><td>12/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5488: Update the instance value to Not Satisfied</td><td/></tr><tr><td>9</td><td>13/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5511: Corrected expression for EvidenceReceipt, EvidenceResultType, TimeDecisionReason</td><td/></tr><tr><td>10</td><td>14/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5288 : DB changes to remove MinimumPayableAmount, LeaveTimeMinimumAmount and LeaveTimeMinimumAmountBasis attributes from LeavePlanPaidLeave entity</td><td/></tr><tr><td>11</td><td>14/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5285 : Changes to remove minimumPayableAmount, leaveTimeMinimumAmount and leaveTimeMinimumAmountBasis fields from leavePlanPaidLeave along with all Validators</td><td/></tr><tr><td>12</td><td>17/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5545: Update the OverrideRuleEligibilityResultType to include Not Known and Partially Met.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>13</td><td>18/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5599: The headers are corrected as needed.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>14</td><td>18/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5571 : Create a Absence Case Java Rule  method to check if the pending Leave Request has any Evidence Result with Evidence Receipt status as Pending</td><td/></tr><tr><td>15</td><td>18/07/2017</td><td>FAB-5272</td><td/></tr></tbody></table></div></div></div>