<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><div class="panel panel-default"><div class="table-responsive"><div class="card sb-card"><div class="card-block"><h3>Reviews created for <Strong>v_marwaha</Strong> for sprint <Strong>Derry 2</Strong></h3><p>This gives a way to access review timelines, see revisions, see files, see comments, apply/reference key word indicators.</p></div></div><div class="panel-body"><table class="table"><thead><tr><th>
									#
								</th><th>
									Create Date
								</th><th>
									Summary
								</th><th>
									Revisions
								</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>1</td><td>17/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6216:Message displayed on selection of drop down options, Clear Messages on Ajax method.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>2</td><td>18/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6304: Add Evidence Status (EvidenceResultType) field to SelectedLeavePlan entity</td><td/></tr><tr><td>3</td><td>18/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6285: Revert the changes made related to automatic Task creation with description when Protocol exists with one Decision day is allowed</td><td/></tr><tr><td>4</td><td>18/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6285: Automatic Task creation with description when Protocol exists with one Decision day is allowed</td><td/></tr><tr><td>5</td><td>18/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6298 - Implement the Service for validation and use it on widget to show message if validation exists</td><td/></tr><tr><td>6</td><td>18/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6270:add in a manual task where Exceptions Restrictions exist.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>7</td><td>21/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6330: Application crashes when Click on Apply button in Manage Time with no Decision Day are selected</td><td/></tr><tr><td>8</td><td>21/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6225 : Partially Met plans cannot be progressed?</td><td/></tr><tr><td>9</td><td>21/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6319 - Make change to attach Employee entity instead of Employer to Adjudicate Absence Task</td><td/></tr><tr><td>10</td><td>21/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6319 - Make change to attach Employee entity instead of Employer to Adjudicate Absence Task</td><td/></tr><tr><td>11</td><td>22/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6311: Status to be N/A when No Evidence needed</td><td/></tr><tr><td>12</td><td>22/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6327 - Update Overall Evidence Status when capturing Evidence through EForm</td><td/></tr><tr><td>13</td><td>22/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6308 - Add Evidence Status and corresponding icon to Manage Request tab\'s SLP List Views.(View and Edit Leave Request Pages)</td><td/></tr><tr><td>14</td><td>22/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6326 - Update Overall Evidence Status when manually Manage Evidence</td><td/></tr><tr><td>15</td><td>22/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6307 - Add Evidence Status and corresponding icon to Leave Details Tab - Selected Leave Plans List view</td><td/></tr><tr><td>16</td><td>22/08/2017</td><td>FAB-1987:Fixed Selenium nightly failed test for Evidence Decision</td><td/></tr><tr><td>17</td><td>23/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6309: Overall Evidence status defaults to PLEASE_SELECT (displayed as N/A).</td><td/></tr><tr><td>18</td><td>23/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6328 - Update Overall Evidence Status when Evidence is overdue (15 Days after)</td><td/></tr><tr><td>19</td><td>23/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6375:Widget failed error displayed on click on view history in Leave Details page, change @Inject</td><td/></tr><tr><td>20</td><td>24/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6402 - Modify the the Table models on Leave Details tab, and View/Edit Leave request to return TaEnum for getEvidenceStatus()</td><td/></tr><tr><td>21</td><td>29/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6429:Selenium test for Overall Evidence Status</td><td/></tr></tbody></table></div></div></div>