<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><div class="panel panel-default"><div class="table-responsive"><div class="card sb-card"><div class="card-block"><h3>Reviews created for <Strong>v_ranah</Strong> for sprint <Strong>Derry 3</Strong></h3><p>This gives a way to access review timelines, see revisions, see files, see comments, apply/reference key word indicators.</p></div></div><div class="panel-body"><table class="table"><thead><tr><th>
									#
								</th><th>
									Create Date
								</th><th>
									Summary
								</th><th>
									Revisions
								</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>1</td><td>31/08/2017</td><td>FAB-1987:Fixed Selenium nightly failed tests</td><td/></tr><tr><td>2</td><td>31/08/2017</td><td>FAB-6340 Bug fix Info message should not be displayed when manager job end date is not specified</td><td/></tr><tr><td>3</td><td>01/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6621: Validation is not necessary when MTI is set to Does Not Apply.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>4</td><td>01/09/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 : Fixed Selenium Nightly Failed test for Employee Hierarchy</td><td/></tr><tr><td>5</td><td>01/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6567 Remove framework related Info message while overriding Eligibility Result Page</td><td/></tr><tr><td>6</td><td>01/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6566 Remove framework related Info message for Manage Overdue Evidence page</td><td/></tr><tr><td>7</td><td>01/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6607 Introduced new doamin instances for time decision status and reason</td><td/></tr><tr><td>8</td><td>01/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6607 Added the subset ManageTimeDecisionStatus</td><td/></tr><tr><td>9</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6654: Performance improvement of auto evaluation of Decision Days - related to MTI</td><td/></tr><tr><td>10</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6629 - Warning if Decision Reason not specified (UI)</td><td/></tr><tr><td>11</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6463 : Selenium Re factoring for Update Availability Decision status from Allowed to Time Available</td><td/></tr><tr><td>12</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6458 : Selenium Re factoring for Auto Adjudication Decision set to \'Time Available\' and Reason to blank</td><td/></tr><tr><td>13</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6645 Web layer modifications for Override EligibilityResult page to implement FDP-4985 Solution</td><td/></tr><tr><td>14</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6644 Display message when deny decision is selected and reason is please select</td><td/></tr><tr><td>15</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6639 Code refactoring based on TimeDecisionStatus enum changes to include TimeAvailable</td><td/></tr><tr><td>16</td><td>04/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6607 Fixed the subset issue for \'Time Available\' and modified the subset name to ManualTimeAvailable</td><td/></tr><tr><td>17</td><td>05/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6472 Consider both \'Approved\' and \'Time Available\' Days while calculating Projected Balance</td><td/></tr><tr><td>18</td><td>05/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6670 Use subset to display Pending, Time available and Denied in Manage time</td><td/></tr><tr><td>19</td><td>05/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6640 Re factor method names to removed Allowed and include Time Available</td><td/></tr><tr><td>20</td><td>05/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6662 Update info message for AC-04</td><td/></tr><tr><td>21</td><td>06/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6646 - Update service layer to update DecisionDay status and reason</td><td/></tr><tr><td>22</td><td>06/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6692 Modify the implementation to refresh the Decision Reason drop down based on change of Decision Status.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>23</td><td>07/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6728 Update the code for available balance calculation to consider Approved days instead of Time Available</td><td/></tr><tr><td>24</td><td>08/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6735 - Check if the Selected leave Plan\'s Eligibility Status is not Partially Met before doing auto evaluation of decision days.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>25</td><td>09/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6760 - Format the Date displayed in the Manual Intervention Task Description, to display Date without time.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>26</td><td>09/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6738 : Availability Decision Reason Validation on Manual Evaluation of Availability</td><td/></tr><tr><td>27</td><td>09/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6700:Selenium test to evaluate AutoDecision For manually Approved Leave Request</td><td/></tr><tr><td>28</td><td>09/09/2017</td><td>FAB-6743 Refresh the code to display the updated selected leave plans status</td><td/></tr></tbody></table></div></div></div>