<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><div class="panel panel-default"><div class="table-responsive"><div class="card sb-card"><div class="card-block"><h3>Reviews created for <Strong>higginst</Strong> for sprint <Strong>Donegal 5</Strong></h3><p>This gives a way to access review timelines, see revisions, see files, see comments, apply/reference key word indicators.</p></div></div><div class="panel-body"><table class="table"><thead><tr><th>
									#
								</th><th>
									Create Date
								</th><th>
									Summary
								</th><th>
									Revisions
								</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>1</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3608 delete the insert sql of the Substitution of Paid Leave protocols.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>2</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FAB-2942 </td><td/></tr><tr><td>3</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FFO-40833  refactor display case tabs to only find elements using the second half of the css id, as the tabs id\'s change when there is a wizard associated with the case - i.e</td><td/></tr><tr><td>4</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 refactor create active paid leave selects and sendkeys for ajax</td><td/></tr><tr><td>5</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 update column headers after check in to source </td><td/></tr><tr><td>6</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 refactor PersonDTO so tests use it correctly</td><td/></tr><tr><td>7</td><td>11/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 refactor flaky tests to wait for presence of different fields after ajax / page render</td><td/></tr><tr><td>8</td><td>12/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3681 Update Paper Intake to show new FDP Calendar</td><td/></tr><tr><td>9</td><td>12/05/2017</td><td>FAB-2990 Implement domain logic for the replacement of Absence Reasons and Relationship magnifier glass by drop downs</td><td/></tr><tr><td>10</td><td>12/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3621: Junits for Absence Period pop ups in intake</td><td/></tr><tr><td>11</td><td>12/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 Refactor SSN number so the first digit cannot be \'9\'</td><td/></tr><tr><td>12</td><td>12/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3637 Updated javadoc</td><td/></tr><tr><td>13</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1616 Split Request Overview step into 2 widgets</td><td/></tr><tr><td>14</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 Introduce method to send CTRL + A and then a value to a field</td><td/></tr><tr><td>15</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 Remove selection of identification type until code is in place to select valid SSN numbers</td><td/></tr><tr><td>16</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 method to generate a valid SSN</td><td/></tr><tr><td>17</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3434 Added method to get case owner as string</td><td/></tr><tr><td>18</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-2975 Updated all tests in the intake page to use new parent</td><td/></tr><tr><td>19</td><td>15/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1988 Fix build and change test to not use TA</td><td/></tr><tr><td>20</td><td>16/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3675: Updated work calendar reference under Absence Case</td><td/></tr><tr><td>21</td><td>16/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3767 Fix injection loop between AbsenceCaseService and LeaveRequestPersistenceService</td><td/></tr><tr><td>22</td><td>16/05/2017</td><td>FDP-4319 OCOccupation deepCopy doesn\'t copy the new fields</td><td/></tr><tr><td>23</td><td>16/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3787: Refactor TimeSpan to AbsenceTimeSpan to avoid problems because there is a class in com.fineos.frontoffice.bo also called TimeSpan</td><td/></tr><tr><td>24</td><td>16/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3427 Split out mapping logic so it is re-useable for group claims</td><td/></tr><tr><td>25</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FDP-4372: Added locking method to use the WorkCalendarWrapperWidgetProxy with PRE-JEE transactions.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>26</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3676: Added JUnit for the Intake work calendar tag.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>27</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3812: Added business entities lock.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>28</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1988: Fix build</td><td/></tr><tr><td>29</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FDP-4320: [ABSENCE] Work Pattern start date field</td><td/></tr><tr><td>30</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 including a waitForStaleness after a sendKeysAndTab as page refreshes</td><td/></tr><tr><td>31</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3795 Added size and description annotations</td><td/></tr><tr><td>32</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3750 Updated XML config of the case</td><td/></tr><tr><td>33</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3733 Configure B-build end point and real implementation</td><td/></tr><tr><td>34</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-2975 Updated all tests in the packages to use new parent.</td><td/></tr><tr><td>35</td><td>17/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1988 Fix build due to missing ACF.URL property following merge</td><td/></tr><tr><td>36</td><td>18/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3674: Work pattern start date</td><td/></tr><tr><td>37</td><td>18/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 Disabling tests that will fail due to xpath issue </td><td/></tr><tr><td>38</td><td>18/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1988 Fix build and test attempt</td><td/></tr><tr><td>39</td><td>19/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3834: Disable time fields after Apply patter to the calendar</td><td/></tr><tr><td>40</td><td>19/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 Adding Leave Plan Decision Recording tests to nightly suite</td><td/></tr><tr><td>41</td><td>19/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3637 Changed 200 tests to not use TA</td><td/></tr><tr><td>42</td><td>20/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3738 Refactored claims listeners to have parent class and use template pattern</td><td/></tr><tr><td>43</td><td>22/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3744 Implement Web Application Logic for dropdowns for Absence Reasons and relationships</td><td/></tr><tr><td>44</td><td>22/05/2017</td><td>FAB-360 Fix sonar critical issue</td><td/></tr><tr><td>45</td><td>22/05/2017</td><td>FAB-2991 Selenium for the replacement of the magnifier glass with dropdowns</td><td/></tr><tr><td>46</td><td>22/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 Refactor test to perform an Open Party to fix locking error</td><td/></tr><tr><td>47</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-2991 Selenium for the replacement of the magnifier glass with dropdowns</td><td/></tr><tr><td>48</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-000 FineosDMSStorageLocation will default to /temp</td><td/></tr><tr><td>49</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3738 Set the effective date on the case based on the first date of disability</td><td/></tr><tr><td>50</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3738 Create the occupation and earnings on the claim</td><td/></tr><tr><td>51</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3738 Bug in expected return to work date</td><td/></tr><tr><td>52</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3729 Correctly set and send the intake source</td><td/></tr><tr><td>53</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3884 Absence side changes for new enum package and attribute</td><td/></tr><tr><td>54</td><td>23/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3884 Replaced NotificationMethod with IntakeSource and Regenerated BOs</td><td/></tr><tr><td>55</td><td>24/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3901: Update the HTML Doc Generation</td><td/></tr><tr><td>56</td><td>24/05/2017</td><td>FAB-1987 remove unused method</td><td/></tr><tr><td>57</td><td>24/05/2017</td><td>FAB-3738 Issue with claim failing when notifier not specified</td><td/></tr><tr><td>58</td><td>24/05/2017</td><td>FAB-000 review board</td><td/></tr></tbody></table></div></div></div>